{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "#",
            "question": "Each question consist of two words which have a certain relationship to each other followed by four pairs of related words, Select the pair which has the same relationship.",
            "options": [
                "<b> Click here</b> if you have reviewed all the instructions and question details."
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "DIVA:OPERA",
            "options": ["producer:theatre", "director:drama", "conductor:bus", "thespian:play"],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "GRAIN:SALT",
            "options": ["shard:pottery", "shred:wood", "blades:grass", "chip:glass"],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "THRUST:SPEAR",
            "options": ["mangle:iron", "scabbard:sword", "bow:arrow", "fence:epee"],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "PAIN:SEDATIVE",
            "options": ["comfort:stimulant", "grief:consolation", "trance:narcotic", "ache:extraction"],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "LIGHT:BLIND",
            "options": ["speech:dumb", "language:deaf", "tongue:sound", "voice:vibration"],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "WAN:COLOUR",
            "options": ["corpulent:weight", "insipid:flavour", "pallid:complexion", "enigmatic:puzzle"],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "PORK:PIG",
            "options": ["rooster:chicken", "mutton:sheep", "steer:beef", "lobster:crustacean"],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "AFTER:BEFORE",
            "options": ["first:second", "present:past", "contemporary:historic", "successor:predecessor"],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "INDIGENT:WEALTHY",
            "options": ["angry:rich", "native:affluent", "gauche:graceful", "scholarly:erudite"],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "DISTANCE:MILE",
            "options": ["liquid:litre", "bushel:corn", "weight:scale", "fame:television"],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "TEN:DECIMAL",
            "options": ["seven:septet", "four:quartet", "two:binary", "five:quince"],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "MUNDANE:SPIRITUAL",
            "options": ["common:ghostly", "worldly:unworldly", "routine:novel", "secular:clerical"],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "ARMY:LOGISTICS",
            "options": ["business:strategy", "soldier:students", "war:logic", "team:individual"],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "GRAVITY:PULL",
            "options": ["iron:metal", "north pole:directions", "magnetism:attraction", "dust:desert"],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "FILTER:WATER",
            "options": ["curtail:activity", "expunge:book", "edit:text", "censor:play"],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "HOPE:ASPIRES",
            "options": ["love:elevates", "film:flam", "fib:lie", "fake:ordinary"],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "CORPOREAL:SPIRITUAL",
            "options": ["mesa:plateau", "moron:savant", "foreigner:immigrant", "pedagogue:teacher"],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "question": "SYMPHONY:COMPOSER",
            "options": ["Leonardo:music", "Fresco:painter", "colours:pallet", "art:appreciation"],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
  }
  